<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FreeBSD Handbook on FreeBSD Documentation Portal</title>
    <link>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FreeBSD Handbook on FreeBSD Documentation Portal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>BSD 2-clause &#39;Simplified&#39; License</copyright><atom:link href="https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Part I. Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/parti/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/parti/</guid>
      <description>This part of the handbook is for users and administrators who are new to FreeBSD. These chapters:
   Introduce FreeBSD.
  Guide readers through the installation process.
  Teach UNIX® basics and fundamentals.
  Show how to install the wealth of third party applications available for FreeBSD.
  Introduce X, the UNIX® windowing system, and detail how to configure a desktop environment that makes users more productive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part II. Common Tasks</title>
      <link>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/partii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/partii/</guid>
      <description>Now that the basics have been covered, this part of the book discusses some frequently used features of FreeBSD. These chapters:
   Introduce popular and useful desktop applications: browsers, productivity tools, document viewers, and more.
  Introduce a number of multimedia tools available for FreeBSD.
  Explain the process of building a customized FreeBSD kernel to enable extra functionality.
  Describe the print system in detail, both for desktop and network-connected printer setups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part III. System Administration</title>
      <link>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/partiii/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/partiii/</guid>
      <description>The remaining chapters cover all aspects of FreeBSD system administration. Each chapter starts by describing what will be learned as a result of reading the chapter, and also details what the reader is expected to know before tackling the material.
 These chapters are designed to be read as the information is needed. They do not need to be read in any particular order, nor must all of them be read before beginning to use FreeBSD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part IV. Network Communication</title>
      <link>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/partiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/partiv/</guid>
      <description>FreeBSD is one of the most widely deployed operating systems for high performance network servers. The chapters in this part cover:
   Serial communication
  PPP and PPP over Ethernet
  Electronic Mail
  Running Network Servers
  Firewalls
  Other Advanced Networking Topics
   These chapters are designed to be read when the information is needed. They do not need to be read in any particular order, nor is it necessary to read all of them before using FreeBSD in a network environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Part V. Appendices</title>
      <link>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/partv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/partv/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FreeBSD Glossary</title>
      <link>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/glossary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/glossary/</guid>
      <description>This glossary contains terms and acronyms used within the FreeBSD community and documentation.
 A  ACL  See Access Control List.
 ACPI  See Advanced Configuration and Power Interface.
 AMD  See Automatic Mount Daemon.
 AML  See ACPI Machine Language.
 API  See Application Programming Interface.
 APIC  See Advanced Programmable Interrupt Controller.
 APM  See Advanced Power Management.
 APOP  See Authenticated Post Office Protocol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colophon</title>
      <link>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/colophon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/colophon/</guid>
      <description>This book is the combined work of hundreds of contributors to &amp;#34;The FreeBSD Documentation Project&amp;#34;. The text is authored in AsciiDoc.
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/introduction/</guid>
      <description>Abstract
 Welcome to FreeBSD! This handbook covers the installation and day to day use of FreeBSD {rel140-current}-RELEASE, {rel132-current}-RELEASE and FreeBSD {rel124-current}-RELEASE. This book is the result of ongoing work by many individuals. Some sections might be outdated. Those interested in helping to update and expand this document should send email to the {freebsd-doc}.
 The latest version of this book is available from the FreeBSD web site. Previous versions can be obtained from https://docs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FreeBSD Handbook</title>
      <link>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/book/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://free.bsd-doc.org/en/books/handbook/book/</guid>
      <description>Abstract
 Welcome to FreeBSD! This handbook covers the installation and day to day use of FreeBSD 14.0-RELEASE, 13.2-RELEASE and FreeBSD 12.4-RELEASE. This book is the result of ongoing work by many individuals. Some sections might be outdated. Those interested in helping to update and expand this document should send email to the FreeBSD documentation project mailing list.
 The latest version of this book is available from the FreeBSD web site.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
